[
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df3ec30e857ca65fb3f08"
    },
    "question": "Do I need to have any skiing experience to take lessons at Ride Gudauri?",

    "answer": "No prior experience is necessary! We cater to all skill levels, from complete beginners to advanced skiers. Our certified instructors will tailor lessons to your individual abilities.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T05:53:48.959Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T05:53:48.959Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df8140e83df735878f908"
    },
    "question": "What level am I?",
    "answer": "Find out how to classify yourself to your instructor, and get your lessons started on the right foot. Knowing your level will help set the tone for your lesson, and kick your progression into high gear.\nBeginner (Level 1):\nDescription: This level is for individuals who have never skied before or have minimal experience.\nSkills:\nLearning how to put on and take off ski equipment.\nMastering the basic stance and balance on skis.\nLearning to glide, make turns, and control speed on gentle slopes.\nDeveloping the ability to stop safely.\nIntroduction to using ski lifts.\nIntermediate (Level 2):\nDescription: Participants at this level have basic skiing skills and are ready to progress to more challenging terrain.\nSkills:\nImproving turning skills on varied terrain.\nBuilding confidence on steeper slopes.\nIntroduction to carving turns.\nLearning to ski parallel and link turns smoothly.\nDeveloping basic skills for handling different snow conditions.\nAdvanced Intermediate (Level 3):\nDescription: Skiers at this level are comfortable on most intermediate slopes and are ready for more advanced techniques.\nSkills:\nMastering parallel skiing on steeper slopes.\nIntroduction to off-piste (ungroomed) terrain.\nImproving carving techniques.\nRefining pole usage for balance and turning.\nBuilding confidence in various snow conditions.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:11:32.146Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:11:32.146Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df84c0e83df735878f90b"
    },
    "question": "Where is the meeting location for Ski/snowboard lesson?",
    "answer": "Ride Gudauri Ski School offers multiple meeting locations, including:\n- At the top of the gondola lift, by the Ride Gudauri flag.\n- At the bottom of the gondola lift, in front of Dunkin Donuts.\n- Near the lift passes sales office at Hotel Marco Polo. - On the slope by the Ride Gudauri flag near Hotel Gudauri Lodge.\n- If you're renting equipment from us, we'll meet you next to Hotel Carpe Diem Gudauri, and you'll go directly from there to the central lift.\nOur team will contact you to agree on the point of meeting, taking into consideration your place of residence for added convenience.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:12:28.669Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:12:28.669Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df8680e83df735878f90e"
    },
    "question": "How do I pay for my lesson and equipment rental?",
    "answer": "Payment is made in person at the meeting spot before the activity begins. We accept cash and credit/debit cards. Please check with our team for any specific payment details related to your reservation.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:12:56.847Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:12:56.847Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df8dc0e83df735878f913"
    },
    "question": "How do I get in touch with Ride Gudauri for additional \"question\"s or concerns?",
    "answer": "If you have any further inquiries, feel free to contact our team through the provided contact information on our website. We're here to assist you and make your experience with Ride Gudauri memorable.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:14:52.886Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:14:52.886Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df8ed0e83df735878f916"
    },
    "question": "What should I wear and bring for my ski lesson?",
    "answer": "Dress in layers with waterproof clothing, wear gloves, and bring goggles. Don't forget to bring your ski boots if you have them. If you're renting equipment, we have everything you need at our facilities.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:09.040Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:09.040Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df9000e83df735878f919"
    },
    "question": "Can I rent ski equipment from Ride Gudauri?",
    "answer": "Yes, we offer ski equipment rentals. You can rent skis, boots, and poles from our on-site facilities. Our staff will ensure you have the right gear for a comfortable and enjoyable experience.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:28.623Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:28.623Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df9100e83df735878f91c"
    },
    "question": "What happens in case of bad weather on the day of my reservation?",
    "answer": "Your safety is our priority. In the event of unfavorable weather conditions, we may need to reschedule or, if necessary, cancel the activity. We'll do our best to communicate any changes well in advance.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:44.570Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:15:44.570Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df94f0e83df735878f91f"
    },
    "question": "How many ski lessons do I need?",
    "answer": "We highly recommend booking at least 4 lessons for everybody of any ability. This gives you enough time with the instructor to really focus on specific aspects of technique and improve your all-around skiing/snowboarding to build confidence in new terrain and have more fun on the mountain. Even highly advanced skiers and riders notice huge changes after 4 lessons with a professional instructor. Skiing and snowboarding are sports which you can never stop improving at, and the better you get, the more fun you have!",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:16:47.791Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:16:47.791Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df9690e83df735878f922"
    },
    "question": "How far in advance do i need to book?",
    "answer": "As soon as possible! We highly recommend booking your ski or snowboard instructor as soon as you confirm the dates of your ski trip to Georgia. We are often fully booked over a month in advance for the February midterm holidays.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:17:13.172Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:17:13.172Z"
    }
  },
  {
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "669df9730e83df735878f925"
    },
    "question": "I want morning lessons but they are sold out, what do I do?",
    "answer": "There are a lot of benefits to snowboarding or skiing in Gudauri in the afternoon! The slopes are less crowded, the sun has warmed the snow to make it softer and easier to ski/snowboard on, everybody enjoys skiing more at the warmest time of day when your fingers donâ€™t freeze, and we tend to have more availability for lessons in afternoons.",
    "titleId": {
      "$oid": "669df3d830e857ca65fb3f05"
    },
    "createdAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:17:23.935Z"
    },
    "updatedAt": {
      "$date": "2024-07-22T06:17:23.935Z"
    }
  }
]
